* Currency
    --------
    
    Currency Afghanistan (AFN ؋) Åland Islands (EUR €) Albania (ALL L) Algeria (DZD د.ج) Andorra (EUR €) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (XCD $) Antigua & Barbuda (XCD $) Argentina (USD $) Armenia (AMD դր.) Aruba (AWG ƒ) Ascension Island (SHP £) Australia (AUD $) Austria (EUR €) Azerbaijan (AZN ₼) Bahamas (BSD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (BDT ৳) Barbados (BBD $) Belarus (USD $) Belgium (EUR €) Belize (BZD $) Benin (XOF Fr) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (BOB Bs.) Bosnia & Herzegovina (BAM КМ) Botswana (BWP P) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (BND $) Bulgaria (BGN лв.) Burkina Faso (XOF Fr) Burundi (BIF Fr) Cambodia (KHR ៛) Cameroon (XAF Fr) Canada (CAD $) Cape Verde (CVE $) Caribbean Netherlands (USD $) Cayman Islands (KYD $) Central African Republic (XAF Fr) Chad (XAF Fr) Chile (USD $) China (CNY ¥) Christmas Island (AUD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (AUD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (KMF Fr) Congo - Brazzaville (XAF Fr) Congo - Kinshasa (CDF Fr) Cook Islands (NZD $) Costa Rica (CRC ₡) Côte d’Ivoire (XOF Fr) Croatia (EUR €) Curaçao (ANG ƒ) Cyprus (EUR €) Czechia (CZK Kč) Denmark (DKK kr.) Djibouti (DJF Fdj) Dominica (XCD $) Dominican Republic (DOP $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (EGP ج.م) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (XAF Fr) Eritrea (USD $) Estonia (EUR €) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (ETB Br) Falkland Islands (FKP £) Faroe Islands (DKK kr.) Fiji (FJD $) Finland (EUR €) France (EUR €) French Guiana (EUR €) French Polynesia (XPF Fr) French Southern Territories (EUR €) Gabon (XOF Fr) Gambia (GMD D) Georgia (USD $) Germany (EUR €) Ghana (USD $) Gibraltar (GBP £) Greece (EUR €) Greenland (DKK kr.) Grenada (XCD $) Guadeloupe (EUR €) Guatemala (GTQ Q) Guernsey (GBP £) Guinea (GNF Fr) Guinea-Bissau (XOF Fr) Guyana (GYD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (HNL L) Hong Kong SAR (HKD $) Hungary (HUF Ft) Iceland (ISK kr) India (INR ₹) Indonesia (IDR Rp) Iraq (USD $) Ireland (EUR €) Isle of Man (GBP £) Israel (ILS ₪) Italy (EUR €) Jamaica (JMD $) Japan (JPY ¥) Jersey (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (KZT 〒) Kenya (KES KSh) Kiribati (USD $) Kosovo (EUR €) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (KGS som) Laos (LAK ₭) Latvia (EUR €) Lebanon (LBP ل.ل) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Liechtenstein (CHF CHF) Lithuania (EUR €) Luxembourg (EUR €) Macao SAR (MOP P) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (MWK MK) Malaysia (MYR RM) Maldives (MVR MVR) Mali (XOF Fr) Malta (EUR €) Martinique (EUR €) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (MUR ₨) Mayotte (EUR €) Mexico (USD $) Moldova (MDL L) Monaco (EUR €) Mongolia (MNT ₮) Montenegro (EUR €) Montserrat (XCD $) Morocco (MAD د.م.) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (MMK K) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (AUD $) Nepal (NPR ₨) Netherlands (EUR €) New Caledonia (XPF Fr) New Zealand (NZD $) Nicaragua (NIO C$) Niger (XOF Fr) Nigeria (NGN ₦) Niue (NZD $) Norfolk Island (AUD $) North Macedonia (MKD ден) Norway (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (PKR ₨) Palestinian Territories (ILS ₪) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (PGK K) Paraguay (PYG ₲) Peru (PEN S/.) Philippines (PHP ₱) Pitcairn Islands (NZD $) Poland (PLN zł) Portugal (EUR €) Qatar (QAR ر.ق) Réunion (EUR €) Romania (RON Lei) Russia (USD $) Rwanda (RWF FRw) Samoa (WST T) San Marino (EUR €) São Tomé & Príncipe (STD Db) Saudi Arabia (SAR ر.س) Senegal (XOF Fr) Serbia (RSD РСД) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (SLL Le) Singapore (SGD $) Sint Maarten (ANG ƒ) Slovakia (EUR €) Slovenia (EUR €) Solomon Islands (SBD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (GBP £) South Korea (KRW ₩) South Sudan (USD $) Spain (EUR €) Sri Lanka (LKR ₨) St. Barthélemy (EUR €) St. Helena (SHP £) St. Kitts & Nevis (XCD $) St. Lucia (XCD $) St. Martin (EUR €) St. Pierre & Miquelon (EUR €) St. Vincent & Grenadines (XCD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Sweden (SEK kr) Switzerland (CHF CHF) Taiwan (TWD $) Tajikistan (TJS ЅМ) Tanzania (TZS Sh) Thailand (THB ฿) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (XOF Fr) Tokelau (NZD $) Tonga (TOP T$) Trinidad & Tobago (TTD $) Tristan da Cunha (GBP £) Tunisia (USD $) Türkiye (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (AUD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (UGX USh) Ukraine (UAH ₴) United Arab Emirates (AED د.إ) United Kingdom (GBP £) United States (USD $) Uruguay (UYU $) Uzbekistan (UZS ) Vanuatu (VUV Vt) Vatican City (EUR €) Venezuela (USD $) Vietnam (VND ₫) Wallis & Futuna (XPF Fr) Western Sahara (MAD د.م.) Yemen (YER ﷼) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)
    
    Currency
    --------
    
    United States (USD $)

[Free Shipping for: U.S. & Canadian orders > $100 USD and International > $200 USD](https://support.vinegarsyndrome.com/en-US/store-policies---faq-293565 "https://support.vinegarsyndrome.com/en-US/store-policies---faq-293565")

    * #### [Sub-Labels](#)
        
    * #### [Releases](#)
        
    * #### [Format](#)
        
    * #### [Packaging](#)

    * #### [Labels A-H](#)
        
    * #### [Labels I-Z](#)
        
    * #### [Collections](#)
        
    * #### [Format / Packaging](#)

    * #### [Merchandise](https://vinegarsyndrome.com/collections/merch)
        
    * #### [Genres A-G](#)
        
    * #### [Genres H-Z](#)
        
    * #### [Merch Vendors](#)

Privacy Policy
==============

**Privacy Policy (updated 8/25/17)**  
  
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  
  
**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?**  
  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.  
  
**When do we collect information?**  
  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or enter information on our site.  
  
**How do we use your information?**  
  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
• To quickly process your transactions.  
• To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.  
  
**How do we protect your information?**  
  
We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.  
An external PCI compliant payment gateway handles all CC transactions.  
We do not use Malware Scanning.  
  
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.  
  
We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.  
  
All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.  
  
**Do we use ‘cookies’?**  
  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
  
We use cookies to:  
• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.  
• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
  
If users disable cookies in their browser:  
If you turn cookies off, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.  
  
**Third-party disclosure:**  
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.  
  
**Third-party links**  
  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
  
**Google**  
  
Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
We have not enabled Google AdSense on our site but we may do so in the future.  
  
**California Online Privacy Protection Act**  
  
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at:  
http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf  
  
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:  
Users can visit our site anonymously.  
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.  
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:  
• On our Privacy Policy Page  
Can change your personal information:  
• By logging in to your account  
  
**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**  
  
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.  
  
**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**  
  
It’s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking  
  
**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**  
  
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.  
  
**Fair Information Practices**  
  
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.  
  
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify you via email  
• Within 7 business days  
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.  
  
**CAN SPAM Act**  
  
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
  
We collect your email address in order to:  
• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.  
• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service  
• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.  
  
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:  
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.  
• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.  
• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.  
• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.  
• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.  
• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.  
  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at  
contact@vinsyn.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.  
  
**Contacting Us**  
  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.  
Vinegar Syndrome  
100 Congress Street  
Bridgeport, CT 06604  
United States  
contact@vinsyn.com  

475-731-1778

**Last Edited on 2017-08-25**

### Info

### Shop

### Explore

### Connect

Sign up for our mailing list to stay up to date on new releases, sales & events and more!

### Follow us!

Copyright © 2024 [Vinegar Syndrome](https://vinegarsyndrome.com/).  [Powered by Shopify](https://www.shopify.com/?utm_campaign=poweredby&utm_medium=shopify&utm_source=onlinestore)

American Express Apple Pay Diners Club Discover Meta Pay Google Pay Mastercard PayPal Shop Pay Venmo Visa

Cart
----

0 Item(s)

### Stay in the know!

Join our mailing list for updates on new releases, promotions & events.

\*By completing this form you're signing up to receive our emails and can unsubscribe at any time.

Your are successfully subscribed for email notifications.

✖

Notify me when available

We will send you a notification as soon as this product is available again.

 Do you want to get recurring notifications?

Your email is required

Notify Me

We don't share your email with anybody

x
